<resources>

    <string name="app_name">GIF Player - OmniGIF</string>

    <string name="short_desc">OmniGIF - your best Android GIF/APNG/WEBP animation player!</string>

    <string name="full_desc">
        OmniGIF is your best Android GIF player, maker and editor.

        OmniGIF is also your best choice for playing APNG (animated PNG) and animated WEBP on Android, you just need to enable it in the settings menu.

        With OmniGIF, you can:
        ◆ Easily mange your GIFs, video clips and photos.
            • Browse your media database in a fancy gallery mode
            • Navigate device storage with a handy file explorer
            • Hide private files secretly to hide them from other application
            • Label your favorite item to find them easily later
        ◆ Play your content with plenty of options:
            • Fast and slow playback
            • Play forward and backward
            • Frame by frame playing
            • Zoom in and out, and panning freely
            • Seamless gesture control for brightness, volume, speed and progress
            • Slide show with mixed GIF, video and static images
            • Share your GIF, video or photo to Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Messenger, Line, WhatsApp, Gmail and any other applications
            • Set your cool GIF or video as wallpaper of your device
        ◆ Edit your GIFs or create new GIF from your video clip
            • Resizing and cropping
            • Trimming and resampling
            • Add caption and watermark
            • Many other color/encoding options
            • Optimizing to shrink file size to use it as emoji and send it to your Facebook, Twitter,, Messenger, Line friends.
        ◆ Navigate popular Internet GIF/video resources
            • OmniGIF provides a nice Reddit explorer
            • You can search or add a SubReddit by its name
            • More online GIF websites will be supported in future

        There are also plenty of additional options which can help you tune this application to serve your at its best.
    </string>

</resources>
